Hey guys, welcome back to another video today.
We're going to be doing a review of the Walmart
plus features that they just implemented or the Walmart grocery
delivery service.
Now this video is not sponsored but if you guys
would like $10 off on your first order over $50
too afraid to use my Walmart referral link,
you'll get $10 and I'll also get $10.
OK, so all you have to do is download the
Walmart app on your phone and your start screen after
you log in.
Should look something like this.
You'll have the option of pickup and delivery or to
shop.
On walmart.com, so you're going to click on pickup and
delivery an already have it set up to deliver to
my address,
which I will be censoring out.
Now you could see that Walmart Plus is here,
so we're going to Click to learn more,
and we're going to sign up for the 15 day
trial.
As you could see, you could get unlimited deliveries,
member prices on fuel, and more,
only at $12.95 per month or $98 per year.
Evidently, Walmart plus pays for itself after two deliveries,
which I could test it because I was looking at
prices.
If I wanted something delivered to me without Walmart.
Plus it cost anywhere between 8:00 and $10,
you can shop with the same everyday low prices that
you would find at the store,
and if you wanted to check to see if this
was available in your area,
you would just type in your address right there and
click on check address.
So my address is available for this feature,
so I'm going to start my 15 day free trial.
Now confirm my address free unlimited delivery from groceries to
gadgets here.
Today are everyday low prices etc.
And you could even have the mobile scan and go
feature.
So if you wanted to just go to Walmart you
could scan each item with your phone and just pay
out with Walmart Pay which is pretty cool if you
want to go into just get one item real quick.
We're going to try the month to month after the
free trial.
Start Walmart for free so I have a 15 day
free trial which is what we're testing this out with
extended child to 30 days.
Answer 3. Questions so that war cost could work harder
for you.
Alright, let's extend it still happens,
including you. How many people live in your home?
Do you share your home with kind of subscriptions?
Do you already have OK?
So now instead of 15 days I have 30 days
and those are very very easy questions so continue to
benefits.
OK, so now that I have signed up for Walmart
plus I could reserve a time so let's see what
times I have available.
At this point I'm recording this at 8:30 AM,
so my earliest delivery time for.
Today would be at 1:00 PM to 2:00 PM,
so we're going to click on that.
So about five hours later so you can plan ahead.
Maybe plan for the next day if you want delivery
for the following day for like a party or something.
So let's see what we have available to us here.
As you could see, you could even get bananas,
eggs, milk, bread, water.